# Frank Skyler Kidd

18504 126<sup>th</sup> Ave NE Apt 1901, Bothell WA f.s.kidd@gmail.com, (425) 876 2036, www.linkedin.com/in/skylerkidd

## **Personal Statement**

As a student at the University of Washington, I am heavily involved in various tech communities and projects. Holding leadership roles in multiple organizations, I have strived to empower others to learn and create exciting personal projects. Through my work at Techstars, participation at hackathons and Startup Weekend events, and work on the Microsoft IoT grant, I have worked in fast-paced team environments using cutting-edge technologies.

# **Work Experience**

UW Bothell / Microsoft – IoT Student Developer
December 2015 – Present

**Techstars – Technical Associate** June 2015 – Present

**UP Global – Support Technician** February 2015 – June 2015

**UP Global – Operations Manager** September 2014 – January 2015

**UP Global – Regional Coordinator** March 2014 – September 2014

## **Volunteer Experience**

**DubHacks – Executive Board Member** August 2014 – Present

**Startup Weekend - Facilitator** August 2014 – November 2014

**Startup Weekend - Organizer** February 2014 – August 2014

## **Education**

## **University of Washington – Computer Science and Software Engineering**

Fall 2013 – Fall 2016 (Expected)

Data Structures, Algorithms, and Discrete Mathematics I (CSS 342)
Data Structures, Algorithms, and Discrete Mathematics II (CSS 343)
Management Principles for Computing Professionals (CSS 350)
Software Engineering (CSS 360)
Analysis and Design (CSS 370)
Hardware and Computer Organization (CSS 422)
Operating Systems (CSS 430)
Multimedia and Signal Computing (CSS 457)
Database Systems (CSS 475)

## **Cascadia Community College**

Fall 2011 - Spring 2013

### Skills

## **Technical**

Java, Python Html & CSS, JavaScript AngularJS, MongoDB, NodeJS

#### **Personal**

Event Management, Organizational Development, Community Outreach